Guide to the Frank Whitson Fetter Papers, 1902-1992
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Publications, 1857-1992, undated (bulk, 1940-1979). (Box 15)
  - Restricted (Box 22)
    - Economist in Parliament: (Box 26)
      - Research: (Box 26)
        - Lords journals, 1812-1868, undated (Box 27)
        - Misc. research, 1941, undated (Box 27)
        - Attwood, M., undated (Box 27)
        - Attwood, T., 1938-1963, undated (Box 27)
        - Baring, A. (Ashburn), undated (Box 27)
        - Baring, F., undated (Box 27)
        - Baring, William Bingham, undated (Box 27)
        - Blackwood, Frederick Temple Hamilton-Temple, undated (Box 27)
        - Blake, William John, undated (Box 27)
        - Boyd, undated (Box 27)
        - Brougham (Brougham and Vaux), undated (Box 27)
        - Buller, Charles, undated (Box 27)
        - Butt, undated (Box 27)
        - Cavendish, Lord Frederick Charles, undated (Box 27)
        - Cayley, undated (Box 27)
        - Clay, undated (Box 27)
        - Cobden, undated (Box 27)
        - Cobbett, undated (Box 27)
        - Copleston (Ilandaff), undated (Box 27)
        - Davenport, undated (Box 27)
        - Drummond, undated (Box 27)
        - Fawcett, undated (Box 27)
        - Fielden, undated (Box 27)
        - Graham, undated (Box 27)
        - Finlay, 1970, undated (Box 27)
        - Gilbert (Giddy), undated (Box 27)
        - Gisbourne, undated (Box 27)
        - Gladston, William Ewart, undated (Box 27)
        - Goschen, undated (Box 27)
        - Grenfell, undated (Box 27)
        - Grey (Howick), 1971, undated, (2 folders) (Box 27)
        - Grote, undated (Box 27)
        - Hankey, undated (Box 27)
        - Hawes, Sir Benjamin, undated (Box 27)
        - Huskisson, undated (Box 27)
        - Jacob, undated (Box 27)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 28)
      - Research: (Box 28)
        - Jenkinson (Hawksbury, Liverpool), undated (Box 28)
        - Leveson-Gower, Granville George, undated (Box 28)
        - Herries, 1955, undated (Box 28)
        - Horner, undated (Box 28)
        - Hubbard, undated (Box 28)
        - Hume, undated (Box 28)
        - King, undated (Box 28)
        - Leveson-Gower, Edward Frederick, undated (Box 28)
        - Lewis, undated (Box 28)
        - Lowe, undated (Box 28)
        - Lowe, Robert, undated (Box 28)
        - Loyd (Overstone), undated (Box 28)
        - Loyd, Samuel Jones, 1969-1971, undated (Box 28)
        - Lubbock, Sir John, undated (Box 28)
        - Lyall, George, undated (Box 28)
        - Maberly, Col. William Leader, undated (Box 28)
        - Maitland (Lauderdale), undated (Box 28)
        - McCulloch, John R., undated (Box 28)
        - Mill, undated (Box 28)
        - Molesworth, undated (Box 28)
        - Morrison, undated (Box 28)
        - Muntz, undated (Box 28)
        - Northcote, undated (Box 28)
        - O'Connell, Daniel, undated (Box 28)
        - Parnell, Sir Henry, undated (Box 28)
        - Peacocke, George Montague Warren, undated (Box 28)
        - Peel, undated (Box 28)
        - Pleydell-Bouverie, Edward, undated (Box 28)
        - Petty-Fitzmaurice (Lansdowne), undated (Box 28)
        - Pryme, undated (Box 28)
        - Ricardo, D., undated (Box 28)
        - Ricardo, J. L., undated (Box 28)
        - Rice, (Monteagle), undated (Box 28)
        - Romilly, Sir John, undated (Box 28)
        - Rose, undated (Box 28)
        - Sadler, undated (Box 28)
        - Sinclair, undated (Box 28)
        - Smith, John Abel, undated (Box 28)
        - Spencer (Althorp), undated (Box 28)
        - Strutt, Edward, undated (Box 28)
        - Thompson, Thomas Perronet, undated (Box 28)
        - Thornton, Henry, 1947, undated (Box 28)
        - Torrens, Robert, undated (Box 28)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 28)
      - Research: (Box 28)
        - Vansittart (Bexley), undated (Box 28)
        - Villiers, Charles Pelham, undated (Box 28)
        - Villiers, George, undated (Box 28)
        - Villiers, Thomas Hyde, undated (Box 28)
        - Warburton, Henry, undated (Box 28)
        - Western (Western), undated (Box 28)
        - Whateley (Dublin), undated (Box 28)
        - Whitmore, undated (Box 28)
        - Wilson, undated (Box 28)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 28)
      - Research: Name of Economists in Parliament: (Box 28)
        - Attwood, Matthias, 1962-1970, undated (Box 28)
        - Attwood, Thomas, 1955-1963, undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Baring, Alexander, 1970-1972, undated (Box 28)
        - Baring, Francis, undated (Box 28)
        - Boyd, Walter, 1971, undated (Box 28)
        - Brougham, Henry, undated (Box 28)
        - Burke, Edmond, 1978, undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Butt-Isaac, 1971, undated (Box 28)
        - Cayley, Edward S., undated (Box 28)
        - Clay, Sir William, 1971, undated (Box 28)
        - Cobbett, William, undated (Box 28)
        - Cobden, Richard, 1972, undated (Box 28)
        - Copleston, Edward, 1971, undated (Box 28)
        - Davenport, Edward D., 1967, undated (Box 28)
        - Drummond, Henry, undated (Box 28)
        - Fawcett, Henry, undated (Box 28)
        - Fielden, John, undated (Box 28)
        - Finlay, Kirkman, 1971-1975, undated (Box 28)
        - Graham, Sir James R. G., 1971, undated (Box 28)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 29)
      - Research: Name of Economists in Parliament: (Box 29)
        - Grey, Henry George, undated (Box 29)
        - Grote, George, 1974-1978, undated (Box 29)
        - Hankey, Thomson, undated (Box 29)
        - Gisborne, Thomas, undated (Box 29)
        - Goschen, George Joachim, undated (Box 29)
        - Fitzmaurice, Henry Petty, undated (Box 29)
        - Forster, William E., undated (Box 29)
        - Gilbert, Davies, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Herries, John Charles, 1957-1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Hodgson, Kirkman, Daniel, undated (Box 29)
        - Horner, Francis, undated (Box 29)
        - Hubbard, John Gellibrand, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Hume, Joseph, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Huskisson, William, undated (Box 29)
        - Jacob, William, undated (Box 29)
        - Jenkinson, Charles, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - King, Peter, undated (Box 29)
        - Lewis, Sir George Cornewall, undated (Box 29)
        - Maitland, James, undated (Box 29)
        - Mill, John Stuart, 1973-1981, undated (Box 29)
        - Molesworth, Sir William, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Morrison, James, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Muntz, George Frederick, undated (Box 29)
        - Northcote, Sr. Stafford Henry, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Peel, Sir Robert, 1958, undated (Box 29)
        - Pryme, George, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Ricardo, David, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Ricardo, John Lewis, undated (Box 29)
        - Ricardo, Samson, undated (Box 29)
        - Rice, Thomas Spring, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Rose, George, 1972, undated (Box 29)
        - Sadler, Michael Thomas, undated (Box 29)
        - Scrope, George Julius Poulett, 1980, undated (Box 29)
        - Sinclair, Sir John, undated (Box 29)
        - Spencer, John Charles, undated (Box 29)
        - Stanhope, Philip Henry, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Thompson, Charles Edward Poulette, undated (Box 29)
        - Thornton, Henry, undated (Box 29)
        - Vansittart, Nicholas, 1972, undated (Box 29)
        - Watkin, Sir Edward William, undated (Box 29)
        - Western, Lord Charles Callis, 1970-1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Whately, Richard, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Whitmore, William Wolryche, undated (Box 29)
        - Wilkinson, William Arthur, undated (Box 29)
        - Wilmont (Horton), Sir Robert John, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Wilson, James, 1971, undated (Box 29)
        - Wodehouse, John, undated (Box 29)
        - Notes: Location of manuscript, 1970, undated (Box 29)
        - Parliamentary history, undated, (5 folders) (Box 29)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 30)
      - Research: (Box 30)
        - Parliamentary history, undated (Box 30)
        - Select and non-select commons, (3 folders) (Box 30)
        - Speeches and economists, undated (Box 30)
        - Subjects: (Box 30)
          - Index, undated (Box 30)
          - Education (Box 30)
          - Test Oaths (Box 30)
          - Catholic disabilities (Box 30)
          - Church of Ireland (Box 30)
          - Jewish disabilities (Box 30)
          - War with France (Box 30)
          - Foreign relations #7, undated (Box 30)
          - Parliamentary Reform #8, undated (Box 30)
          - Slave trade, undated (Box 30)
          - Slavery, undated (Box 30)
          - Colonial affairs, undated (Box 30)
          - Australia, undated (Box 30)
          - Canada, undated (Box 30)
          - Transportation, undated (Box 30)
          - Hours of work, undated (Box 30)
          - Legislation for Protection of Women and Children, undated (Box 30)
          - Civil list, pensions, and sinecures, undated (Box 30)
          - Ireland, undated (Box 30)
          - Tithes, undated (Box 30)
          - India, undated (Box 30)
          - East India Co., undated (Box 30)
          - America Revolution, undated (Box 30)
          - American relations, undated (Box 30)
          - Flogging in Army and Navy, undated (Box 30)
          - Army and Navy administration, undated (Box 30)
          - Taxation, undated (Box 30)
          - Distillery Tax, undated (Box 30)
          - Newspaper, tax, undated (Box 30)
          - Corn laws, undated (Box 30)
          - Bank of England, undated (Box 30)
          - Banking, undated (Box 30)
          - Trade Unions--apprenticeship, undated (Box 30)
          - Emigration, Immigration, undated (Box 30)
          - Civil rights, undated (Box 30)
          - Legal system, undated (Box 30)
          - Libel, undated (Box 30)
          - Navigation acts, undated (Box 30)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 30)
      - Research: (Box 30)
        - Subjects: (Box 30)
          - Consult of Lords and members of Parliament, undated (Box 30)
          - Scotland, undated (Box 30)
          - Information on Public Business, undated (Box 30)
          - Public debt and budget, undated (Box 30)
          - China, undated (Box 30)
          - Poor laws, undated (Box 30)
          - Poor laws (Ireland), undated (Box 30)
          - Royal family, undated (Box 30)
          - American Civil War, undated (Box 30)
          - Orders in council, undated (Box 30)
          - Denmark, undated (Box 30)
          - Sugar distillery, undated (Box 30)
          - Irish banking, undated (Box 30)
          - Bank of Ireland, undated (Box 30)
          - Civil Service, parliament and government organizations, undated (Box 30)
          - Voluntary aids, undated (Box 30)
          - Church of England, undated (Box 30)
          - Customs, imports, exports, undated (Box 30)
          - Vaccination, undated (Box 30)
          - Annuities, undated (Box 30)
          - Maynooth College, undated (Box 30)
          - Agriculture, undated (Box 30)
          - Pool writ, undated (Box 30)
          - Museums and antiquities, undated (Box 30)
          - Personal honors and claims, undated (Box 30)
          - Exchequer and lottery bills, undated (Box 30)
          - Internal commerce, undated (Box 30)
          - Unclassified topics, undated (Box 30)
          - Mr. Palmers claims, undated (Box 30)
          - Marine Insurance (Box 30)
          - Queen Caroline, undated (Box 30)
          - Remarks on King's speeches, undated (Box 30)
          - Joint stock Cos. (West India Company), undated (Box 30)
          - Cape Colony, undated (Box 30)
          - Monetary standard, undated (Box 30)
          - Beer, undated (Box 30)
          - Unemployment, undated (Box 30)
          - Women's rights, undated (Box 30)
        - Votes: (Box 30)
          - undated (Box 30)
          - By subjects, undated (Box 30)
          - In Parliament, 1780, Aug.-1883, Aug. 14, (2 folders) (Box 30)
    - Economists in Parliament: (Box 31)
      - Research: (Box 31)
        - Votes in Parliament, 1834, Feb. 4-1885, undated, (6 folders) (Box 31)
      - Reviews, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Unpublished Articles and Pamphlets (Box 31)
    - “Articles on History of Economic Theory,” manuscripts and notes, 1958 (Box 31)
    - Britain Prepared to Give America her Freedom, Viceroy States, 1943 (Box 31)
    - Franklin Scott on the Trail, the Stream and the Portage, 1974, Feb. (Box 31)
    - Geography and the Tariff, 1934, Feb. (Box 31)
    - Hudson Bay Blankets--Reflections on a Minor Tariff Issue: Correspondence, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Inter-country Comparison of the role of Foreign Capital in Economic Development Before 1914, 1968, Feb. (Box 31)
  - Unpublished Articles and Pamphlets (Box 31)
    - “Memorandum on Secretary Morganthau's letter of March 22, 1939...,” manuscripts, 1939 (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1977, (4 folders) (Box 31)
    - “Some Problems of International Income Comparisons,” manuscripts, 1961 (Box 31)
    - Soviet Monetary and Banking Policy, 1931, Aug. (Box 31)
  - Unpublished Books and Manuscripts (Box 31)
    - Foreign Capital in Economic Development: (Box 31)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Box 31)
      - General outline, 1961 (Box 31)
      - Manuscript, 1968-1976, (5 folders) (Box 31)
      - Manuscript, 1962-1970, undated, (3 folders) (Box 32)
      - Notes for manuscript, 1970-1981, undated (Box 32)
      - Research: (Box 32)
        - Australia: (Box 32)
          - Books and articles, undated (Box 32)
          - Butlin/Kuznets, 1960, undated (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous, 1961-1980, undated (Box 32)
          - Notes on readings, 1959-1970, undated (Box 32)
          - Printed material, 1963-1981, undated (Box 32)
          - Statistics, 1970, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
        - BMD29 and Rasmuseen's sample program, undated (Box 32)
        - British theses, undated (Box 32)
      - Manuscript, 1962-1970, undated, (3 folders) (Box 32)
      - Notes for manuscript, 1970-1981, undated (Box 32)
      - Research: (Box 32)
        - Australia: (Box 32)
        - Canada: (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 32)
          - Notes on reading, 1962-1966, undated (Box 32)
          - Printed material, 1967-1960, undated (Box 32)
          - Statistics, undated (Box 32)
        - Charts and tables, undated (Box 32)
        - Countries not covered, 1962-1966, undated (Box 32)
        - Denmark: (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966-1969, undated (Box 32)
          - Notes on reading, 1966-1968, undated (Box 32)
          - Statistics, undated (Box 32)
        - Economic planning, 1966, undated (Box 32)
        - Finland, undated (Box 32)
        - General statistics and charts, undated (Box 32)
        - Italy: (Box 32)
          - Bibliographies, 1953, undated (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous: (Box 32)
            - 1951-1957, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
            - Fenoaltea manuscript, 1968, (3 folders) (Box 32)
            - Notes on reading, 1964-1977, undated (Box 32)
            - Printed material, 1962-1966, undated (Box 32)
        - Italy: Statistics, 1970, undated, (3 folders) (Box 32)
        - Japan: (Box 32)
          - Books and articles, 1966-1970, undated (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 32)
          - Notes on readings, 1962-1970, undated (Box 32)
          - Printed material, 1968-1980, undated (Box 32)
          - Rosovsky manuscript and tables, 1965 (Box 32)
          - Statistics, 1968, undated (Box 32)
        - Miscellaneous: (Box 32)
          - 1968-1980, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
          - Notes and books and articles, 1961-1981, undated, (4 folders) (Box 32)
          - Printed material, 1951-1962, undated, (3 folders) (Box 32)
          - Statistics and notes, 1953-1967, undated (Box 32)
        - Norway: (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous, 1960, undated (Box 32)
          - Notes on reading, 1966-1970, undated (Box 32)
          - Statistics, 1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
        - Rostow: Stages of Economic Growth (Box 32)
        - Sweden: Miscellaneous, 1959, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
        - Sweden: (Box 34)
          - Notes on reading, 1966-1970, undated (Box 34)
          - Statistics, 1961-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 34)
        - Theoretical issues, 1962-1966, undated (Box 34)
        - United States: (Box 34)
          - Books and articles, undated (Box 34)
          - BOP, undated (Box 34)
          - Gallman, 1963, undated (Box 34)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966, undated (Box 34)
          - Printed material, 1961-1967, undated (Box 34)
          - Statistics, 1968-1970, undated, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - International Economic Relations and Economic Development, 1957, June (Box 34)
    - Overend, Gurney: (Box 34)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1992, (3 folders) (Box 34)
      - Manuscripts, 1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - Manuscript revision notes, 1986, undated (Box 34)
      - Outline, undated (Box 34)
      - Research: (Box 34)
        - Accounts, bad and doubtful, undated (Box 34)
        - Bank of England, 1941-1986, undated (Box 34)
        - Bank of Ireland, undated (Box 34)
        - Bankers Almanac, 1984, undated (Box 34)
        - Bankers Magazine, 1869-1883, 1984, undated, (2 folders) (Box 34)
        - Barclay's Bank, 1802-1966, undated (Box 34)
        - Baring Brothers Bank, 1981-1983, undated, (2 folders) (Box 35)
        - Books and articles, 1980-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 35)
        - British Museum and Library, 1983-1984, undated (Box 35)
        - British theses, 1981, undated (Box 35)
        - Burke's Landed Gentry, undated (Box 35)
        - Buxton, undated (Box 35)
        - Clippings: (Box 35)
          - 1866-1868 (Box 35)
          - Davidson and Gordon, 1857-1858 (Box 35)
          - Edward's hearing before bankruptcy court, 1869 (Box 35)
          - Gordon case, 1853-1854 (Box 35)
          - Guildhall, 1866 (Box 35)
          - Judgment at House of Lords in Peek vs. Gurney, 1873 (Box 35)
          - London Times, 1868-1969, (6 folders) (Box 35)
          - Merchants Company, 1869, undated (Box 35)
          - Newspaper cuttings of trial, 1869 (Box 35)
          - The Economist magazine, 1847-1893, 1982, undated (Box 35)
        - Friend's House, 1828-1896, undated (Box 35)
        - Friends Journal magazine, undated (Box 35)
        - Gladstone private papers, undated (Box 35)
        - Glyn, undated (Box 35)
        - Gurney genealogy, 1984-1988, undated (Box 35)
        - House of Lords, 1864-1870, undated, (2 folders) (Box 35)
        - Incorporation papers, undated (Box 35)
        - Law cases, 1872, undated (Box 35)
        - Liquidators' reports, 1866-1868, undated (Box 35)
        - Lloyd's Bank, 1834-1947, undated (Box 35)
        - Magazines, 1982-1986, undated (Box 35)
        - Midland Bank, undated (Box 35)
        - Miscellaneous: (Box 35)
          - 1971-1982, undated (Box 35)
          - Newspaper clippings and notes, 1866-1869, undated (Box 35)
          - Testimony, 1819-1864, undated (Box 35)
          - Testimony notes, undated (Box 35)
        - Notes: London Times, undated (Box 35)
        - Parliament, 1983, undated (Box 35)
        - Parliamentary debate, 1986, undated (Box 35)
        - Parliamentary reports and hearings, 1851-1866, 1984, undated (Box 35)
        - Punch magazine, 1866-1869 (Box 35)
        - Rothchild, 1813-1817, 1982, undated (Box 36)
        - Sale of estates of partners, 1983-1987, undated (Box 36)
        - Suspense and guarantee account, 1987, undated (Box 36)
        - Testimony: Samuel Gurney and D. B. Chapman, 1963-1978 (Box 36)
        - Wills and death notice, 1984, undated (Box 36)
- General Research, 1923-1981. (Box 36)
  The second largest series contains much of Fetter's collected research, and consists of three subseries: Alphabetical Files, Cards and Film, and Published Articles and Pamphlets. The Alphabetical Files are organized by topic and include magazine and newspaper clippings, bank records, court records, statistics, charts and tables, notes on readings, and bibliographies. A second set of alphabetical research files consists of microfilm and index cards. The final sub-series contains correspondence and background research for Fetter's articles and pamphlets, and complements the Published Articles and Pamphlet's sub-series in the Publications Series.
  - Alphabetical Files (Box 36)
    - Act of Union, undated (Box 36)
    - American politics, undated (Box 36)
    - Articles: Miscellaneous before 1935 (Box 36)
    - Assassination at Sarajevo, undated (Box 36)
    - Attwood, Mathias--episode of, 1962 (Box 36)
    - Bank of England, undated (Box 36)
    - Bank of England--Meetings of Stockholders of the Bank of England: 1809-1875, 1959, Jan. (Box 36)
    - Barbecue, undated (Box 36)
    - Birmingham newspaper, 1833, 1961, undated (Box 36)
    - British Cabinet memoranda, 1959-1985, undated (Box 36)
    - British history--research, undated, (7 folders) (Box 36)
    - British research, 1956-1980, undated, (6 folders) (Box 36)
    - British review: (Box 36)
      - Articles, 1967-1969, undated (Box 36)
      - Notes, undated (Box 36)
      - Translation, 1826-1842, 1969-1978, undated (Box 36)
    - Bullion operation of the Bank of England, 1797-1811, undated (Box 37)
    - Chile--miscellaneous, undated (Box 37)
    - Christ of the Andes: (Box 37)
      - 1927-1938, undated (Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1927-1933 (Box 37)
    - Circular to bankers, 1958-1962, undated (Box 37)
    - Cobbett and relations with Ricardo, 1955-1964, undated (Box 37)
    - College aims and objectives, 1956-1963, undated (Box 37)
    - Committee appendices, 1832 (Box 37)
    - Committee on bank acts, 1858, (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Constitution, undated (Box 37)
    - Dawes Commission, 1968-1969, undated (Box 37)
    - Declaration of Independence, 1972-1976, undated (Box 37)
    - Devaluation, 1967 (Box 37)
    - Dictionaries: (Box 37)
      - English phonology, undated (Box 37)
      - French, 1941-1956 (Box 37)
      - German, undated (Box 37)
      - Italian, undated (Box 37)
      - Russian, undated (Box 37)
      - Spanish, undated (Box 37)
    - Discussion of measurement of effects of trade agreements, 1937, undated (Box 37)
    - Dublin Exchange, 1811-1826, 1946 (Box 37)
    - East India Co. bullion movements, undated (Box 37)
    - Economic adjustments to disarmament, 1963-1964 (Box 37)
    - Elections: (Box 37)
      - Parliament, 1958-1971, undated (Box 37)
      - States--clippings, 1968 (Box 37)
    - England--private parliament papers, 1955-1979 (Box 37)
    - English banking histories, 1952-1963, undated (Box 37)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von, 1976, undated (Box 38)
    - Hume, 1971-1972, undated (Box 38)
    - Inflation, 1967-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Irish elections, 1750-1832 (Box 38)
    - Language, 1932-1981, undated (Box 38)
    - Latin America, 1953-1980, undated (Box 38)
    - Law, 1935-1937, undated (Box 38)
    - Location of economists' papers, undated (Box 38)
    - Malthus, Thomas: correspondence and research, 1953-1965, undated (Box 38)
    - Manchester Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 38)
    - Mathematical economics, 1960, 1963 (Box 38)
    - McCloskey, 1956-1959 (Box 38)
    - Mill, John Stuart, 1955-1964, undated (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 38)
      - 1947-1962, undated (Box 38)
      - Bibliography, undated (Box 38)
      - Notes on reading, 1938-1977, undated, (6 folders) (Box 38)
      - Research, 1941-1986, undated, (4 folders) (Box 38)
    - Money and Gold Standard: (Box 38)
      - Clippings, 1932-1936, 1946 (Box 38)
      - Printed material, 1927, 1930-1933 (Box 38)
    - Nanga Parbot, 1953 (Box 38)
    - National income, 1938-1960, undated (Box 39)
    - Newspapers: (Box 39)
      - Index, undated (Box 39)